

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Coding Languages

Python, C, Java, PHP, C#

Frameworks/Systems

Deep Learning

- TensorFlow, Keras, PyTorch

Data Science

- NumPy, Pandas, Matplotlib, Seaborn, Scikit-Learn Others
- Ruby on Rails, Laravel, Matlab

COURSES

Neural Networks and Deep Learning/Coursera
Al for Everyone/Coursera

Machine Learning Crash Course/Google Developers
Signal and Image Processing, Deep Learning/TED

University

Database Design and Programming with SQL/ORACLE
Machine Learning, Deep Learning/IEEE TURKEY
SECTION

Radar Systems Fundamentals/ASELSAN DATAI TEAM

- Statistics & Python: Basic Statistics Science
- Deep Learning and Python: Deep Learning
- Machine Learning and Python
- Data Visualization
- Data Science and Python: Expertise

RESEARCH PAPERS

- Tooth Detection and Numbering with Instance Segmentation in Panoramic Radiographs
- <u>Automatic Dental Segmentation Module</u>
 <u>Supported by Artificial Intelligence for Dentistry</u>
 Students Education

CONTACT

Email: dilara.zdemir19980@gmail.com

Phone: +90 553 961 21 07

LinkedIn:https://www.linkedin.com/in/dilaraozdemir/

Github: https://github.com/dilaraozdemir **Website:** https://dilaraozdemir.github.io/

REFERENCES

Assist. Prof. Caner OZCAN

CEO, Founder of SimurgAl **Phone:** (370) 418 7050

Mail: canerozcan@karabuk.edu.tr

Dilara Ozdemir

COMPUTER ENGINEER

ABOUT ME

I received a bachelor's degree in Computer Engineering from Karabuk University. Since November 2020, I have been working as an Artificial Intelligence Developer at SimurgAl, located in the Technology Development Office of Karabuk University. Between January 2021 and July 2021, I worked as an intern researcher within the scope of TUBITAK STAR in the Artificial Intelligence Assisted Automatic Analysis of Images Obtained in Dentistry (DentiAssist) project that we are developing within our company. Our project titled Analysis of Panoramic Dental Images with Deep Learning Methods, which we developed with my supervisor, received support within the scope of 2209-A University Students Research Projects Support Program.

EXPERIENCE

AI DEVELOPER

SimurgAI | Nov. 2020 -

- Object Detection, Segmentation and Analysis on MR Images via Transfer Learning

RESEARCH INTERN

TUBITAK | Feb. 2021 -

- Artificial Intelligence Based Automatic Analysis of Images Obtained in Dentistry (DENTIASSIST)

SUMMER INTERN

Karabuk University | Jun. 2020 - Aug. 2020

- Data Science, Data Analysis
- Machine Learning
- Deep Learning

LABORATORY ASSISTANT

Karabuk University | Sep. 2019 - Mar. 2020

- Student Assistant of CME112-Programming Languages Course

EDUCATION

KARABUK UNIVERSITY (GPA 3.24 / 4.00)

Computer Engineering Department | 2016 - 2021

- 100% English Computer Engineering Department.

ANADOLU UNIVERSITY

Justice Department | 2019 -

- 2nd grade student.

PROJECTS

ANALYSIS OF PANORAMIC DENTAL IMAGES USING ARTIFICIAL LEARNING TECHNIQUES

SimurgAI | Oct. 2020 -

As the workload of dentists is too high, treatments cannot be followed regularly, and because of the COVID-19 epidemic and similar epidemic risks in the future, less doctorpatient contact is required, as a solution, artificial intelligence supported dental radiography analysis is performed.

SEGMENTATION OF BITEWING INTRA ORAL X-RAY IMAGES WITH MASK R-CNN DEEP LEARNING MODEL

SimurgAI | Oct. 2020 -

In the treatment and diagnosis process of teeth that need to be examined in detail in the field of dental health, bitewing intraoral radiography images are used. It is an ideal diagnostic method for the detection of recurrent caries that cannot be directly seen in the mouth, especially at the interface of small and large molars and under restorations.

CLASSIFICATION OF HAND WRIST X-RAY IMAGES

Medathon | Apr. 2021

VGG-16, DenseNet and MobileNet networks were operated with 1000 Hand Wrist X-ray images submitted under the competition. Transfer Learning methods were used.